Guide to the Yale-China Association Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale-China Association administrative records
1903-1989
1970-1989
RU 233
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
33.25
The records consist of administrative files, annual reports, correspondence, oral histories, photographs, audiovisual material, and memorabilia documenting the operations of the Yale-China Association. The files were maintained by the Yale-China Association New Haven office.
Yale-China Association
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Associated Materials
Related material: Yale-China Association Records (RU 232), Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The records are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files, annual reports, correspondence, oral histories, photographs, audiovisual material, and memorabilia documenting the operations of the Yale-China Association. The files were maintained by the Yale-China Association New Haven office.
Missions -- China; Photographs; Yale-China Association
- Administrative records, 1906-1989; Accession 1991-A-035
  - "A", 4/9/1970-3/29/1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Achilles, H. Laurence, 12/1973-6/6/1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Fund Raising, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Bureau for Medical Aid: Garside, 1/1970-8/1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Dinner, 9/1973-10/18/1973, 10/25/1974, 5/30/1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Dinner and Drama, 8/20/1974-10/16/1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting Material, 10/26/1973-5/28/1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, 6/10/1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting Minutes, 6/10/1968-6/10/1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting Material, 5/28/1976-6/18/1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting Minutes, 5/24/1976-8/23/1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting Materials, 3/15/1977-6/3/1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting Minutes, 4/29/1977-6/3/1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting and Board Meeting, 6/1/1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 6/1/1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, 6/1/1980-6/10/1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 5/1972-6/7192 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report: Preparations for Mailing, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report: Supporting Materials, Bills and Estimates, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 9/6/1975, 5/9/1977, 1977, 12/20/1976-5/29/1979 (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
  - Anthony, Rev. B. Kenneth, 12/6/1978-5/9/1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Apartment- 589A Prospect, 7/10/1970-5/7/1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Appeal Folders: Publicity, 6/11/1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Appeal Letters: Cost Estimate, 9/21/1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Appeal Letters: 1973-1975 Trustee Fund Drive, 12/27/1972-1/28/1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Appeal Letters: Monthly, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Appeal Letters: Printer's Instructions, 10/11/1973-5/19/1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Appeal Letters: Regular and Reminders Mailing Schedule, 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Appeal Letters: Sample Copies, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Appeal Letters: Special, 10/21/1974-11/14/1974, 6/3/1975-6/5/1975 (Box 2, Folder 33-34)
  - Appeal Returns: Monthly Letter Check Off List, 5/72-12/1973, 1/74-6/1975 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - Appeal Returns, Summary and Comparison, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Archives Material, 1967, 1970, 1972, 1973, 1975, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Archives Materials for Files, 8/30/1940-4/19/1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Archives, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Arnold, Lauren (Trustee), 5/8/1967-6/11/1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Arnold, Lauren (Honorary), 9/2/1980-6/22/1988 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Arsenic and Old Lace - a play produced by Yale Bachelors, 3/1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Art Exhibit (Correspondence), 5/23/1974-2/19/1976 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Art Exhibit: Conn. College, Northern Michigan, Skidmore College, Univ. of Bridgeport, 6/7/1973-3/6/1975 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Art Exhibit: Dartmouth College, Penn State, Pittsburgh, 9/14/1973-8/30/1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Art Exhibit: Robert C. Graham, Graham Gallery, 6/15/1976-12/10-1976 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Art Exhibit: Insurance Policy and Storage Contracts, 1/29/1974-11/25/1975 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Art Exhibit: Killiam, 11/13/1975-5/4/1976 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Art Exhibit: Lecture, 8/9/1974-6/2/1975 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Art Exhibit: Price List and Mounting Charges, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Art Exhibit: Prospective Exhibitors, 6/13/1973-8/29/1975 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Art Exhibit: Prospectus and Leaflet, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Art Exhibit: Publicity, 3/28/1974-12/12/1975 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Art Exhibit: Rejections, 9/24/1973-1/27/1975 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Art Exhibit: Sales, 3/6/1974-3/8/1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Art Exhibit: Shipping (Instructions and Papers), 3/26/1972-2/13/1976 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Art Exhibit: Washington, D. C., 6/11/1974-11/22/1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Art Trip: Washington, D. C., 3/1974-7/16/1975 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1903-1974 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Association Publications: Holden and Greene, 12/1976-1981 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Asia Foundation, 9/25/1963-5/14/1974 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Au, Wing Lee: Scholarship Student, Michigan State Univ., 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - "B", 4/9/1970-3/29/1979 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Bachelor Appeal: Clarke Letters, 12/12/1977-2/9/1978 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Bachelor Sample Recruiting Material, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Balance Sheets for Grant Proposals Based on Haskins and Selb Audit, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Bau, Yur-Shen (Biologist, Post-Doctoral Fellow for Academic Year), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Beaver College, Including GLCA Early ASP-Beaver College Relations, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Bell, Richard (Trustee), Prior 7/1980 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Benjamin Franklin Centre: Chinese Univ. of Hong Kong., undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Berger, Harvey J. (Yale Medical School-Travel Grant), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - "Dr. Norman Bethune", 11/13/1979-5/8/1980 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Board Committee: Members' List, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Board Meeting, 9/22/1978 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Board Meeting and Annual Meeting, 6/2/1978 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Board Meeting, 2/23/1979, 4/17/79-11/15/1979, 12/17/1979-1/24/1980 (Box 5, Folder 77-79)
  - Board of Trustees, 1953-1964 (Box 5, Folder 80-86)
  - Board of Trustees, 1965, 1966, 1968-1974, 1976, 1980, 1981, 11/16/1977-4/21/1978, 9/4/1979-5/19/1980, 7/9/1980-8/10/1981, 4/1/1981-12/17/1981, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 87-97)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984-1985, 6/21/1985-6/20/1986 (Box 7, Folder 98-99)
  - Board of Trustees: Committees On Programs and Projects, 10/2/1976-6/3/1977, 8/17/1977-1/20/1979, 1980-1985, 4/17/1985-4/2/1986 (Box 7, Folder 100-107)
  - Board of Trustees: Development Committee, 7/22/1980, 5/27/1975-6/11/1981, 10/2/1981-3/11/1982, 1982-1985, 10/1/1985-6/20/1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 108-115)
  - Board of Trustees: Executive Committee, 11/10/1979-5/24/1979, 7/26/1979-12/7/1979, 1980-1981, 12/17/1981-5/4/1982, 1982-1985, 11/23/1985-6/20/1986 (Box 8, Folder 116-123)
  - Board of Trustees: Finance Committee, 1981-7/16/1982, 8/25/1980-4/21/1983, 10/18/1982-6/21/1984, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 124-127)
  - Board of Trustees: Finance Committee, 1984-4/25/1985, 1979-12/18/1981 (Box 9, Folder 128-129)
  - Board of Trustees: Investment Management Committee, 1983-1985, 5/1983-5/30/1986 (Box 9, Folder 130-132)
  - Board of Trustees: Medical Committee, 10/1980-4/9/1981, 8/26/1981-1/29/1982, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 133-135)
  - Book Orders, 4/3/1967-5/25/1979 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Books: Purchases, 12/31/1975-3/23/1976, 12/29/1978 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Building Fund, 1960's (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Buildings, New (at Shatin Site), 8/18/1970-2/1973 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - "C", 4/9/1978-3/29/1979 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Calendar, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Calendar of Events: Work Schedules, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Chan, Wellington: Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Chan, Yue-Wah: Overseas Fellowship, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Chang, Helen (Yale Medical School), 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Chang, Hsan-Mou (Senior Fellowship), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - H.C. Chang Scholarships: Chang Ya-Shang (1 of 2), 11/30/1951-7/17/1980 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - H.C. Chang Scholarships: Chang Ya-Shang (2 of 2), 1/30/1981-7/7/1980 (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Chang, Teh Ch'ang: Post Graduate Scholar, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 149)
  - Chi (Helen) Proposal, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Children in China: An Update, 1/15/1982-2/2/1982 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - China and Christianity. Yale Divinity School Colloquium, 4/16/82 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - China and Documentary Art, Fall 1983 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - China Council, 1979-8/29/1983, 11/21/1983-11/29/1984, 8/1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 154-156)
  - "China Hands, Old," Publication, 1945, 8/7/1969 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - China Notes: United Board, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - China Programs Night, 1/24/1984 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - China Programs Update (Student Committee), 2/17/1983 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - "China Tomorrow," Sept, 1979, 12/24/1978-11/12/1979 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - China Tour Spring 1982 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - China Tour Spring 1983 (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - China Tour led by Weigle, Fall 1983 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - China Trade Fair, 12/13/1981 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - China Trip: YUAG and Y-in-C A, Fall 1983 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - China Weekend, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Chinese Art, undated (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Chinese Arts Festival, 4/1/1980-10/4/1981 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Chinese Bronzes: Bus Tour to Boston, 7/31/1981-9/23/1981 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Chinese Cooking Classes, 12/1/1976-2/6/1979 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Chinese New Year Party/Cabaret, 2/3/1984 (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Birth of (Story), 1/1970 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Prior to 1/79, 1963-12/28/1978 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Bulletin, 6/1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Commission, undated (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Correspondence, 1/1/1973-9/24/1976 (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Correspondence of Vice Chancellor, 8/31/1973-11/11/1977 (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Chancellor C. M. Li, 12/22/1977-11/15/1978 (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Resolution 1967- CUHK-NAK Relationship, 1/10/1967 (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Dan, Robert, M.D. Director Univ. Health Services, 1/19/1972-11/9/1976 (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Fulton Report, 3/1976-1/4/1977 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Guest House, 7/13/1972-4/3/1973 (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Health Center Drug Donations, 7/24/1967-4/16/1971 (Box 13, Folder 184)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Health Center Gifts, 12/21/1967-12/1976 (Box 13, Folder 185)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Health, Dept. of Policy and Procedure Manual, undated (Box 13, Folder 186)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Health Center Schedule of Payments, undated (Box 13, Folder 187)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Health Center Dedication, 9/30/1971 (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Honorary Degree: C. Mili, undated (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Programs for Exchange Students, 9/28/1975-12/9/1975 (Box 13, Folder 190)
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong: Vice-Chancellor Malin's U.S. Visit, 5/9-10/1978 (Box 13, Folder 191)
  - Ching Ching Dance Troupe, 4/11/1978 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Chou, Eric: A Man Must Choose, Book Reviews, 6/1963 (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Cities in China Series: Xiau, Suzhau, Beijing (films), 3/19/1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 194)
  - Claims Settlement Fund: Memos and Correspondence (1 of 2), undated (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - Claims Settlement Fund: Memos and Correspondence (2 of 2), undated (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - Clarke, Robert: Correspondence in Chronological Order, 7/14/1977-9/18/1979 (Box 14, Folder 197)
  - Clarke, Robert: Former Staff, 5/19/1977-5/31/1985 (Box 14, Folder 198)
  - Classes of 1950-1970: Contribution List, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 199)
  - Codlin, Kenneth (Former Trustee), 6/2/1975-11/14/1978 (Box 14, Folder 200)
  - Coffin, William S. (Former Trustee), 9/18/1967-5/12/1978 (Box 14, Folder 201)
  - Committee on Programs and Projects, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 202-203)
  - Committee on Programs and Projects, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Conference on Priorities for Funding and Development of Chinese Studies, 11/8-9/1973 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Connecticut College and Wellesley College, 1970-1976 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Consortium for Asian Studies: Education in the Schools: CASES David A. Wilson Correspondence, 11/3/1976-3/3/1977 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Contemporary China Study Group, 10/15/1979-2/17/1987 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Contracts and Agreements, 1/4/1974-3/13/1974 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Contributors' Correspondence, 1/1973-12/1973, 1974, 1/1975-6/1975, 7/1975-12/1975, 1/1976-6/1976, 7/1976-12/1976, 1/1977-12/1977 (Box 15, Folder 210-216)
  - Contributors' Letters: Scholarships, 3/1973-9/1973 (Box 15, Folder 217)
  - Contributors' Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Contributors: Special Letters, (Appeal to Close Deficit), 6/1972, 6-7/1973, 10-12/1974 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - Contributors' Letters: Special, 4/1973-7/1973, 5/22/1974-2/19/1975 (Box 16, Folder 220-221)
  - Contributors: Prospective Indivs., 12/1967-6/1973 (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - Contributors to Yale in China By Name in Years, 1972/1973 (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - Contributors to Yale in China By Name, 1973/1974 (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - Correspondence with Auditors, 7/29/1971-1/2/1973 (Box 16, Folder 225)
  - Correspondence, 1/27/1981-12/21/1981 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Committee on Programs and Projects, 10/3/1979-10/28/1979 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - Creed, 10/23/1973-11/12/1973 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - "D", 6/29/1972-9/13/1978 (Box 16, Folder 229)
  - Deborah Darris: Freedman Program, 11/10/1983 (Box 16, Folder 230)
  - Descriptions of its work, 12/23/1974 (Box 16, Folder 231)
  - Development Committee, 8/21/1977-11/2/1977 (Box 16, Folder 232)
  - Development Committee Meeting, 8/13/1976 (Box 16, Folder 233)
  - Divinity School, 1/21/1976 (Box 16, Folder 234)
  - Divinity School Lectures, 2/19/1975 (Box 16, Folder 235)
  - Doctor's Panel, 6/2/1969-10/21/1974 (Box 16, Folder 236)
  - Dowd, Rachel (Honorary Trustee), 3/15/1967-10/10/1979 (Box 16, Folder 237)
  - "E", 8/5/1972-8/1976 (Box 16, Folder 238)
  - Eightieth Anniversary Dinner, 8/1980-4/15/1981 (Box 16, Folder 239)
  - ELIS: CUHK Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - ELIS: HMU Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 241)
  - ELIS: HNU Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 242)
  - ELIS: New Haven Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 243)
  - ELIS: Program Reduction Study, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 244)
  - Elliot, Nellie Memorial Fund, 7/22/1976-3/9/1979 (Box 17, Folder 245)
  - Elsmith, Dorothy Olcott, 3/27/1969-2/19/1984 (Box 17, Folder 246)
  - Executive Committee, 3/15/1973-5/17/1976 (Box 17, Folder 247)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 248)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 17, Folder 249-251)
  - Executive Committee prior 1/79, 2/2/1978-5/2/1978 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - Executive Director's Correspondence Miscellaneous, 8/24/1975-12/19/1979 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Executive Director's Correspondence, 1/1980-9/15/1982, 7/8/1981-12/17/1981, 7/1/1980-12/18/1980, 12/18/1980-6/16/1981 (Box 18, Folder 254-257)
  - "F", 7/7/1973-4/5/1979 (Box 18, Folder 258)
  - Fall Solicitation Letter #3: Attended Programs, 4/4/1975-10/14/1975 (Box 18, Folder 259)
  - Ferguson, Richard C. (Trustee), 6/8/1976-12/15/1987 (Box 18, Folder 260)
  - Films of China, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - Film Policy, Budget, Etc…, undated (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Film Project, Undated, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 263-265)
  - Film Project Description, 7/30/1976 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - Material Sent to People On Evaluation Committee (Box 19)
  - Report on the Yale-China Film Series Project, 8/11/1977 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Film Series on China: Amended Proposal, 1/7/1977; 4/6/1977 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Film Project: Biographies of Scholar Participants, undated (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Film Project: Bibliography for Film #2, undated (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Film Project: Correspondence, 3/3/1975-2/1/1977 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - Film Project: Recent Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Film Project: Correspondence, 1975-1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 273-274)
  - Film Project: Financial Material- Second Quarter, undated (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Film Project: Indiana Audio-Visual, undated (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Film Project: Proposals, undated (Box 20, Folder 277-278)
  - Film Project: Quarterly Reports to NEA, undated (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Film Project: Revised Proposal, 4/6/1977 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Film Project: Yale Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 281)
    General note
    (Charncey and Cabranes)
  - Film Script, undated (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Film series: Revised Proposal, 1/1977 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Film Series: Information, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Films: Archaeology, undated (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - Films: Budget, undated (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - Films: "Culture and Revolution", undated (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - Films: "Last Dynasty", undated (Box 20, Folder 288)
  - Films: "Life in Imperial China", undated (Box 20, Folder 289)
  - Films: Other Outlines, undated (Box 20, Folder 290)
  - Films: Photographic Film Materials Used In Pilot Films, undated (Box 20, Folder 291)
  - Films: Potential Film Purchases or Inquires on Distribution, undated (Box 20, Folder 292)
  - Films: "Republican Revolution", undated (Box 20, Folder 293)
  - Films: "Republican Revolution" Outline, undated (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Films: "Social & Economic Development", undated (Box 21, Folder 295)
  - Films: "Socialist Transformation", undated (Box 21, Folder 296)
  - Film Week, 11/17/1983-1/26/1983 (Box 21, Folder 297)
  - Questions of China Films, undated (Box 21, Folder 298)
  - Final Committee Reports, 11/2/1973, 3/9/1974-6/4/1974, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 299-300)
  - Old Financial Data, 3/26/1969-10/1/1976 (Box 21, Folder 301)
  - Finance Committee, 1975-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 302-303)
  - Finance and Development Committee, 1970-1973, 1/1973-2/1975, 11/1974-7/1975 (Box 21, Folder 304-306)
  - Finance and Development Committee Quarterly Report, 1/1975 (Box 21, Folder 307)
  - Finance and Development Committee, 1977-1978, 2/21/1975-12/12/1979, 2/6/1979-12/20-1979, 1/7/1980-6/25/1980 (Box 21, Folder 308-311)
  - Finance and Development Rohrbach Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 312)
  - Finance Development, 6/1978-9/1978 (Box 22, Folder 313)
  - Finance/Development Meeting: N.Y.C., 6/29/1978-12/1978 (Box 22, Folder 314)
  - Financial Reports, 7/1970-6/30/1971 (Box 22, Folder 315)
  - Financial Statement (Without Audit), 6/30/1971 (Box 22, Folder 316)
  - Finch, Stuart C. (Former Trustee), 2/6/1975-5/3/1977 (Box 22, Folder 317)
  - Foster, Dr. John H., 4/13/1981-3/21/1985 (Box 22, Folder 318)
  - Foundation Fund Raiser: "Council for the Advancement and Support of Education," Bob Clarke, 10/1977 (Box 22, Folder 319)
  - Foundations: National Endowment For the Humanities, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 320)
  - Form Letters: Reminder Cards, 1960-1977 (Box 22, Folder 321)
  - Frankel, David: Acting Representative in Hong Kong, 9/20/1977-2/20/1978 (Box 22, Folder 322)
  - Fulton, R. Brank (Trustee), 6/3/1970-6/19/1980 (Box 22, Folder 323)
  - Fund Raising Institute, 1/1974-12/1975 (Box 22, Folder 324)
  - Fund Raising: Long Range Planning, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 325)
  - Fund Raising Telethon, 6/16/1975, 1973-1974, 9/10/1974, 3/13/1975 (Box 22, Folder 326-329)
  - Fung, Yiu-Fai, Overseas Fellowship, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 330)
  - Fung, Yui-Tong, Post-Doctoral Fellow, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 331)
  - Future Prospects, undated (Box 23, Folder 332)
  - Future Role on Mainland China, 5/2/1972 (Box 23, Folder 333)
  - "G", 7/20/1972-6/21/1979 (Box 23, Folder 334)
  - Galston, Professor Arthur W., 3/16/1972-8/9/1978 (Box 23, Folder 335)
  - Giamatti, A Bartlett, 12/18/1978-2/8/1985 (Box 23, Folder 336)
  - Greene, Phil: Correspondence, 9/4/1932 (Box 23, Folder 337)
  - General Correspondence: Overseas, 10/70-5/1976 (Box 23, Folder 338)
  - Greene, Phillips F. and Ruth, undated (Box 23, Folder 339)
  - Greene, Ruth: Hsiang-Ya Journal, undated (Box 23, Folder 340)
  - Greene, Mrs. Ruth, 4/22/1981-10/9/1986 (Box 23, Folder 341)
  - Grumman, Carol S., 10/24/1978-11/1985 (Box 23, Folder 342)
  - Grumman, Ellsworth (Trustee), 11/1/1974-3/1/1976 (Box 23, Folder 343)
  - "H", 7/11/1972-3/19/1979 (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - Hartford Lecture, 4/1974-12/13/1974 (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - Hayford, Charles: Representative, 1/1978-6/1978, 10/1978-6/1979, 8/1977-12/1977, 7/1978-9/1978 (Box 24, Folder 346-349)
  - Health Committee, 9/1/1967-5/22/1974 (Box 24, Folder 350)
  - Hilgendorf, Mark: correspondence, 12/1969-12/1971 (Box 24, Folder 351)
  - Hilgendorf, William Jr.: Bachelor, 7/16/1967-6/13/1980 (Box 24, Folder 352)
  - Hinck, Henry: Connected with U.S. China Chamber of Commerce, 11/29/1973-11/23/1977 (Box 24, Folder 353)
  - Hisock, Dr. Ira V. (Former Trustee), 7/4/1970-1/17/1986 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - History in Hong Kong Brochure: Proposal of T. Light, 2/14/1967 (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - Ho, Hsiu-hwang, Senior Fellow, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - Ho, Josephine: Overseas Fellowship, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - Ho, Maria Yuen Man (Went to Canada), undated (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - Ho, Suk-Ching: Scholar, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 359)
  - Holden, Reuben (Trustee), 6/9/1969-12/8/1971, 1/3/1972-6/23/1980 (Box 25, Folder 360-361)
  - Hong Kong, 1978-1980, 11/19/1979-6/22/1981, 8/17/1973-7/17/1982, 1982-1985, 7/1985-8/4/1986 (Box 25, Folder 362-369)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence, 6/13/1977-6/15/1981 (Box 25, Folder 370)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 371-372)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence (I), 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 373)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence (II), 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence (I), 7/19/1985-2/26/1986 (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - Hong Kong: Field Staff Office Correspondence, 1/1985-5/1986 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - Hong Kong/New Haven Office Correspondence, 1/11/1979-6/30/1980, 6/12/1981-5/5/1983, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 377-381)
  - Hong Kong/New Haven Office Correspondence, 5/17/1985-4/25/1986 (Box 28, Folder 382)
  - Hong Kong-Representative's Correspondence, 1/1982-6/28/1982 (Box 28, Folder 383-384)